// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: `Sayam is an CSE student and loves coding and decoding. His friends was given the homework of pattern printing but 
  his friend gone some wrong in it. Help Sayam to fix the code. 
  <br><br><fieldset class= 'codebg'> #include&lt;stdio.h&gt;<br>
  int main() {<br>
     int i, j, rows;<br>
     printf("Enter the number of rows: ");<br>
     scanf("%d", &rows);<br>
     for (i = 1; i <= rows; <input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>) {<br>
        for (j = 1; j <input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>; j++) {<br>
           printf(<input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>);<br>
        }<br>
        printf("\\n");<br>
     }<br>
     return 0;<br>
  }</fieldset><br>
  Output must be<br>

1<br>
12<br>
123<br>
1234<br>
12345<br><br><a href='https://www.onlinegdb.com/online_c_compiler' target = '__blank'>Click here to try this code</a>`,
  answer: 'i++<=i"%d",j'
  
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: `You have 7 Rs with you. You go to shop and shopkeeper tells you price as 1 Rs per chocolate.<br>
           He also tells you that you can get a chocolate in return of 2 wrappers,How many maximum chocolates you can eat?<br><br>
           <b>Note:</b>  Answer is a integer. just put the number without any decimal places if its an integer.<br><br>
           <fieldset class='codebg2'><input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput3 ' placeholder = 'Enter answer here'></fieldset>`,
  answer: "13"
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: `One Apple cannot be a Elppa but "itopiNonAvevanoNipoti" can be "iTopiNonAvevanoNipoti"
  So to solve this confusion Ramesh has return the following code.
  Please help him with this.<br>
  <fieldset class='codebg'>
  #include &lt;stdio.h&gt;<br>

#include&lt;string.h&gt;<br>

// Implementing the logic in a function<br>

void isPalindrome(char str[]){<br>

// Initializing indexes<br>

int l = 0;<br>

int h = str<input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>(str) - 1;<br>

// Step 4 to keep checking the characters until they are same<br>

while (h > l){<br>

if (str[l++] != str[h--]){<br>

printf("%s is not a palindrome string\\n", str);<br>

return;<br>

}<br>

}<br>

printf("%s is a palindrome string\\n", str);<br>

}<br>


int <input id = 'codeinput2' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>(){<br>

isPalindrome("level");<br>

isPalindrome("radar");<br>

isPalindrome("Simplilearn";)><br>

return 0;<br>

}<br>
  </fieldset><br>
  <a href='https://www.onlinegdb.com/online_c_compiler' target = '__blank'>Click here to try this code</a>`,
  answer: "lenmain"
  
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: `Ben has 2 integers he tells sum of the integers to person S and product of those number to P. Now What are  those two integers. 
            If integers are x and y then solve :- 5*x+y<br><br>
           <b>Note:</b>  Answer is a integer. just put the number without any decimal places if its an integer.
           <br><br><fieldset class='codebg2'><input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput3' placeholder = 'Enter answer here'></fieldset>`,
  answer: "24"
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: `FIX THE FOLLOWING CODE<br><br>
    <fieldset class='codebg'>
  #include&lt;stdio.h&gt; <br>
  void <input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput ' value='pain'>() <br>
  { <br>
  int preparation=0; <br>
  int <input id = 'codeinput2' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput codeinput2'>;<br>
  father = 0;
  mother = 0;
  int scold = 0;<br>
  if(pass) <br>
  { <br>
    <input id = 'codeinput3' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>("no one cares");<br>
  } <br>
  if(fail) <br>
  { <br>
  while(1) <br>
  { <br>
  father=scold++; <br>
  mother=scold++; <br>
  printf("%d",scold);<br>
  } <br>
  } <br>
  }<br>
  </fieldset><br>
  <a href='https://www.onlinegdb.com/online_c_compiler' target = '__blank'>Click here to try this code</a>`,
  answer: "mainfather,motherprintf"
},

  {
  numb: 6,
  question: `Is it legal for a man to marry his widow's sister ?<br><br>
  <b>Note:</b>Answer must be in lower case.<br><br>
  <b>Hint: </b>Enter yes or no.<br><br><fieldset class='codebg2'><input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput3'placeholder = 'Enter answer here'></fieldset>`,
  answer: "no",
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: `Toadys Weather Report given by Indain Weather Forcasting Team
  is given to you but, the report contains temperature in Celcius, You have to calculate
  its Ferhenite equivalent....<br>
  <fieldset class='codebg'>
  #include&lt;stdio.h&gt;<br>
  int main()<br>
  {<br>
   printf("* www.programmingposts.com *");<br>
   printf("<<< Program for temperature conversion >>>\\n\\n"); <br>
   <input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput' value='int'> cel,far;<br>
   printf("Enter the temperature in Celsius:");<br>
   scanf(<input id = 'codeinput2' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>);<br>
   far=(9*<input id = 'codeinput3' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>)/5+<input id = 'codeinput4' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput'>;<br>
   printf("Equivalent Temperature in Fahrenheit: %f",far);<br>
   return 0;<br>
  }<br>
  </fieldset>
  <a href='https://www.onlinegdb.com/online_c_compiler' target = '__blank'>Click here to try this code</a>`,
  answer: 'float"%f",&celcel32',
 },
{
  numb: 8,
  question: ` It occurs once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in an hour, <br>
  What is it?<br><br>
  <b>Note:</b>Answer must be in lower case.<br><br>
  <b>Hint: </b>It is a character.<br><br><fieldset class='codebg2'><input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput3 ' placeholder = 'Enter answer here'></fieldset>`,
  answer: "m",
 },
 {
  numb: 9,
  question: `There is a building of 100 floors. If an egg drops from the Nth floor or above it will break. If it’s dropped
   from any floor below, it will not break. You’re given 2 eggs. Find N, while minimizing the number of drops for the worst case. <br><br>

  <b>Note: </b>These are very strong eggs because they can be dropped multiple times without breaking as long as 
  they are dropped from floors below their “threshold” floor, floor N. But once an egg is dropped from a floor 
  above it’s threshold floor, it will break. <br><br>
  Find the minimum number of drops required to figure out N.<br><br>
  <fieldset class='codebg2'><input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput3 ' placeholder = 'Enter answer here'></fieldset>`,
  answer: '14'
 
 },
 {
  numb: 10,
  question: `If orange is called blue, blue is called red, red is called yellow, yellow is called green, green is called black, 
  black is called violet and violet is called orange, what would be the colour of blood?<br>1. Red<br>2. Green<br>
  3. Black<br>4. Yellow<br><br>
  <fieldset class='codebg2'><input id = 'codeinput1' name='codearrayinput[]' class = 'codeinput3 ' placeholder = 'Enter your answer'></fieldset>`, 
  answer: "Yellow",
 }
 
]